

SCE, XIDIAN, Xi'an, China, 710071

□ (+86) 159-6320-2817 | **☑** ycding@stu.xidian.edu.cn | **※** matr1x-xdu.github.io



Sep. 2018 - Now

"Be the change that you want to see in the world."

Education

XIDIAN University Xi'an, China

JUNIOR UNDERGRADUATES IN INFORMATION SECURITY

- GPA: 3.8/4, Score (Five Semesters): 88.8
- Academic Ranking: 11/154
- CET4: 596, CET6: 531

Honors & Awards

2019-2020 National Scholarship(3/303) , Model Student of Academic Records, The 1st Prize Scholarship	Xi'an, China
2018-2019 The 1st Prize Scholarship , Model Student of Academic Records, Excellent L eague Member	Xi'an, China
2020-2021 Meritorious Winner(twice), Interdisciplinary Contest In Modeling(ICM)	U.S.A
2020.11 The 1st Price , Mathematical Contest in Modeling	Xi'an, China
2020.10 The Golden Price , China College Students' 'Internet+' Innovation and Entrepreneurship Competition	Xi'an, China
2020.10 The 1st Price(10/200+), Chang'an Cup Electronic Forensics Competition	Xi'an, China

Research Experience _____

Efficient Encrypted Spatiotemporal Data Tracking System Based on Block-DAG

Xi'an, China

TEAM LEADER

Feb. 2021 - June. 2021

- Built blockchain block-DAG architecture to record users' spatiotemporal transaction data, and implement SPECTRE protocol to resolve conflict transaction. Introducing time and space Bloom Filter to improve query efficiency. At Full nodes, BFV full homomorphism encryption is used for transactions, and the data is processed in the form of ciphertext to ensure the privacy and security of users.
- I am jointly responsible for the overall design of the project, including front-end, back-end, mobile client architecture, and the implementation of blockchain system based on Go

Research Project: Anomaly Detection and Recovery of UAV Flight Data

Xi'an, China

Теам Мемвек

May. 2020 - Now

- Based on subspace learning and SVD, the algorithm realizes efficient online recovery of flight data and effectively reduces the resource consumption caused by high-dimensional heterogeneous data. Through the change of subspace, the abnormal score is calculated to realize the efficient identification of abnormal sources and make the results more interpretable.
- It won the provincial gold medal for participating in 'Internet+' Innovation and Entrepreneurship Competition.

Competition Experience _____

Lightweight AI Traffic Filter

Xi'an, China

TEAM LEADER

Feb. 2021 - May. 2021

- After aggregating the original pcap packets, the system uses tshark for offline feature extraction and data processing. To learn the feature pattern of normal traffic and to use sklearn to generate a random forest multi classifier to filter white traffic.
- I am responsible for the implementation of flow aggregation algorithm code and writing project documents.

Student Cadre's Work ____

XIDIAN Vice-monitor, we won the title of "Top Ten Model Classes" in 2019-2020 academic year.

2019 - Now

XIDIAN **Organization Member**, I once had face-to-face communication with school leaders

2018 - Now

Summary_

I am rigorous, hard-working, and have good self-learning ability. I am responsible for programming in every scientific research competition project as being good at engineering programming; I also have good aesthetic ability and document writing ability. In the school as a variety of positions, I has a strong ability to organize cooperation, hence I am suitable for participating in team work. I hope I can devote myself to research, and apply what I have learned to contribute to the construction of national network security and network power.